#fetched from https://opentdb.com/api_config.php
question_data = [
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "hard", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "The song 'Mystery Train' was released by artist 'Little Junior's Blue Flames' in 1953.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "Norwegian producer Kygo released a remix of the song 'Sexual Healing' by Marvin Gaye.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "Pink Guy's debut album was 'Pink Season'.", "correct_answer": "False",
     "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
                                      "question": "The cover of The Beatles album 'Abbey Road' featured a Volkswagen Beetle in the background.",
                                      "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "Soulja Boy's 'Crank That' won a Grammy for Best Rap Song in 2007.",
     "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "EDM label Monstercat signs tracks instead of artists.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "medium", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
                                       "question": "'Neutral Milk Hotel' is a real band.",
                                       "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "Scatman John's real name was John Paul Larkin.", "correct_answer": "True",
     "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
                                       "question": "American rapper Dr. Dre actually has a Ph.D. doctorate.",
                                       "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]},
    {"type": "boolean", "difficulty": "easy", "category": "Entertainment: Music",
     "question": "The music video to The Buggle's 'Video Killed the Radio Star' was the first music video to broadcast on MTV.",
     "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}]
